'ª
girl: Hey, guys, what is this?
Boy: A gate. It connects
the inside and outside.
Girl: Outside?
We've never been outside.
Boy 2: That's because we haven't
left here since being born.
Girl: So is this what mom
always tells us about?
"Never go near the gate or fence
in the back of the forest,
'cause it's dangerous."
Boy 1: She says that,
but it's not true.
Boy 2: It's not?
Girl: Hey, ray,
what would you do outside, huh?
Ray: I don't know. You, Emma?
Emma: I'd ride a giraffe!
Ray: Good luck.
Boy: This gate...
You know, I wonder
what it's really
keeping us protected us from.
'ª
Emma: Good morning, everyone!
Time to get up,
or you'll miss breakfast!
( Children yawning )
( Overlapping chatter )
- Boy: I'm gonna get you!
- Boy 2: Yeah, right!
- ( Boy 1 laughs )
- Girl: Hey!
Stop messing around,
and get ready!
Girl 2: Emma,
I can't put my shoes on!
Boy 3: I don't know
how to tie the laces!
Emma: I'll help you in a second.
There's no need to cry.
( Overlapping chatter )
Emma: Good morning, Don!
Morning, Conny!
You, too, little bunny!
Don: Good morning!
Conny: Good morning, Emma.
Emma: Look.
We're here just in time.
( Boys grunt )
( Boys laugh )
( Emma chuckles )
Now you've done it. ( Growls )
I'm gonna eat you!
Girl 1: And off they go again.
( All laughing )
Boys: Yeah!
Emma: Hey, guys! Good morning!
Boy 4: Hi, Emma. Morning.
Ray: Good morning, Emma.
Boy 4: You're so full of energy,
and you haven't even had
your breakfast yet.
Ray: Come on.
How old are you, five?
Emma: I'm 11, same as you guys
and one of the oldest kids here!
( Woman laughs )
Emma: You're laughing, too, mom?
Mom: Emma, come help me out.
Emma: In a minute!
I wanna redo my entrance,
'cause ray teased me!
Mom: Why change it? It showed
just what I love about you.
Emma: That i'm
five years old at heart?
Mom: Mm-mmm.
That isn't what I meant.
I love how deeply
you care about your family.
Emma: Thank you, mom. I'm glad.
( Giggles )
( Bell rings )
Mom: Good morning to you,
my darling children.
Now let us appreciate
that all 38 of you
are able to live happy lives
under this roof.
We are thankful.
Children: Thank you
for our breakfast.
'ª
mom: Now open wide.
Conny: Ahh.
( Overlapping chatter )
Yummy!
Mom: You're acting
like a little baby,
aren't you, Conny?
Conny: It's okay, right?
Especially today!
Mom: Of course.
Recording: Age 11, type one.
Answer each question
within ten seconds.
When you hear the tone, begin.
( Buzzer )
( Timer ticking )
( Scanner whirring )
'ª
( girl 2 sighs )
( Boy 3 grunts )
( Buzzer )
( Girl 1 sighs )
( Groans )
Boy 1: Well, I think
I got at least half.
Boy 5: That many? Wow!
Conny: I'm jealous. I didn't
get most of the questions.
Mom: Let's quiet down
and go through the results.
Norman, ray, Emma,
perfect scores again!
Fantastic! I'm so proud!
- Emma: Yay!
- ( Children murmuring )
Boy 6: None of us
even come close to those three.
Norman alone's
smarter than all of us combined,
and then there's ray,
who's good at solving
any problem he's faced with.
To top it off,
Emma learns really fast,
so she can keep up
with them, easy.
Girl 1: They say
the house has never had
three kids at this level
together before.
Boy 6: Then, no wonder
mom's proud of them.
- Don: Norman!
- Norman: Hmm?
Don: I'm challenging you to tag!
( Norman chuckles )
( Children cheering, yelling )
( Watch ticking )
( Norman grunts )
( Ray sighs )
( Children yelp )
Don: Come get us, Norman!
We'll outrun you
this time for sure!
Right, Conny?
Conny: Don, thanks for always
being there to help me.
Don: Nah, you don't
have to thank me.
I'll always help anytime,
anywhere you need me.
( Conny giggles ) Shh.
( Don gasps )
Eh? Oh.
( Conny groans )
Don: Judging from the size
of these footprints...
( Chuckles )
You let your guard down, Norman.
- ( Conny chuckles )
- ( Don gasps )
Norman: No, Don. You did.
I tell you this every time.
Your weakness is that you
make a judgment too quickly
and then lose your cool.
( Chuckles )
( Don sighs )
( Overlapping chatter )
Don: What the heck?
He got practically everyone!
Boy 6: That happens
when Norman's it.
Girl 3: There's only
one survivor left.
Girl 1: Yeah.
Emma's still going!
'ª
Emma: Oh.
( Chuckles )
( Norman chuckles )
( Ticking )
( Emma chuckles )
- ( Norman groans )
- ( Emma gasps )
Norman!
Norman: Just pretending.
Emma: What?!
You had me worried about you!
Norman: Emma. Your weakness
is that you're too nice.
( Emma gasps )
I can't believe
he caught me again!
Why do I keep losing?!
So frustrating.
Ray: Question.
What's Norman good at
that you're not?
Emma: Hmm.
Uh, planning ahead
and staying calm?
I guess he's also good
at being smart.
Ray: It's strategy.
Just think. If it's about
simple physical ability,
then you have the upper hand,
but it's more than that.
Norman has brains like no other,
and tag is a game
where you compete with strategy.
Emma: In a game of tag?
Ray: Way I see it,
tag's like chess,
but using your whole body.
Don't you think so, Norman?
Norman: Yeah, sure. But I'd say
that you're more of a tactician
than I am, ray.
Ray: I don't know about that.
Emma: So try to anticipate
the enemy's moves.
Norman: But still,
we can't compare
to mom's ability
to read a situation.
Emma: That's true.
Come to think of it,
none of us have ever been able
to beat her at chess, huh?
- ( Norman chuckles )
- ( Ray sighs )
Don: Norman! Rematch!
Next game, everyone is
gonna be it but you!
Emma: Calm down!
Girl 1:
Don's all worked up again.
( Norman grunts )
( Birds chirping )
( Boy 3 pants )
( Emma gasps )
( Footsteps echoing )
'ª
( Normal footsteps )
( Norman sighs )
Guess you caught me.
'ª
Emma: "Never go near
the gate or fence."
Norman: Yeah,
mom always tells us that,
because going near there
can be very dangerous.
Ray: She says that,
but it's not even true.
Norman: What do
you mean by that?
Ray: Well, look at it.
What part of this
do you find dangerous?
The fence is low,
and I don't see
anything remotely threatening.
Emma: But we should do
what mom told us.
Ray: Uh-huh.
You really love mom, don't you?
- Emma: Sure! Everybody does!
- Don: Hey!
What are you guys
doing way back here?
Girl 1: Oh, is the game over?
Norman: We should call it a day.
If we're out too late,
mom will be worried about us.
Don: Someday...
We'll have to leave here,
won't we?
Boy 6: This is an orphanage.
Of course we'll leave one day,
by the time we turn 12.
Girl 1: You know, it's weird.
None of us
have ever gotten any letters.
- Emma: Letters?
- Girl 1: Yeah,
nothing from any
of our siblings
who've been adopted
over the years.
Norman: Oh, that? I'm sure
they're just being considerate
to their foster parents.
Don: But, still,
we were brought here as babies.
We're the only family we know.
Even if we aren't blood-related,
we're truer siblings than most!
Girl 1: Maybe the outside world
is so incredible
that they've forgotten
all about life at the house.
Emma: Well, in that case,
let's be happy for them.
( Girl 1 groans )
I want to go outside soon, too!
Boy 6: And what
would you do out there?
Girl 1: Isn't it obvious?
Try out new clothes.
- Don: This again.
- Girl 1: I deserve to!
We only have this one uniform!
I read a book one time.
It said the outside world
has hundreds of clothing designs
and patterns,
and I want to wear them all!
Boy 6: I wanna eat
all the yummy food.
Don: I can't wait
to find a cute girl to date.
Girl 1: You realize
that's an insult, don't you?
Don: Oh, I didn't
mean it like that.
Boy 3: I want to see a train!
Don: Hmm, that's a good one.
Emma: And what about you?
Norman: Oh,
well, I want to travel,
to see places
I've never been to before.
Emma: Nice! And you, ray?
Ray: Once outside...
I'd have to learn
to survive first.
Don: You're such a downer.
And you?
Emma: Who, me?
Ray: You want to ride
a giraffe, right?
Emma: I said that?
I guess I don't really
want to leave,
so I'd stay forever.
Don: Come on.
That's not a real answer!
Emma: Why not?
We're all happy here, right?
Ray: Happy? Yeah.
Conny: I promise
to write to you.
I'll write you
stacks of letters!
I won't forget!
You mean too much to me!
- ( Girl 1 sighs )
- Conny: When I grow up,
I want to become a mother
just like mom,
and I'd never even think
about abandoning my children!
Girl 1: You love mom very much,
don't you, Conny?
Conny: Mm.
- ( Giggles )
- ( Wind blows )
( Insects chirping )
Conny: I couldn't run fast,
and I wasn't as clever
as the rest of you are,
but once I leave,
I'll do my best!
And I can,
with little bunny's help!
Don: Conny.
( Conny whimpers )
I don't want to leave you!
I want to stay right here!
Don: Conny, I'll miss you!
( Conny cries )
( Mom humming melody )
Conny: Um, mom,
what song is that?
( Mom continues humming )
( Clock ticking )
Emma: Conny!
You left little bunny?!
Girl 1: Let's hurry
and get the cleaning done.
Oh, little bunny?
But Conny's gone!
Emma: What should we do?
- Ray: There's still time.
- Emma: Huh?
Ray: Yeah, I could see
from the window
that the lights
at the gate were still on.
Mom hasn't come back yet either,
so I don't think
Conny's left just yet.
- Norman: Let's hurry, Emma.
- ( Emma grunts )
( Both panting )
Emma: "Never go near
the gate or the fence."
Norman: Yeah, I know.
We'll both get in trouble later.
Emma: Conny?
( Liquid dripping slowly )
Emma: Is that the truck
that's gonna take Conny
to her new home?
I've never seen a vehicle
in real life.
Eh?
Norman: Hmm.
No one's here.
Emma: Maybe she'll find it
if we leave it in here.
Norman: Yeah, maybe.
Eh?
( Emma shuddering )
'ª
n-Norman.
( Norman grunts )
( Gasps )
( Liquid dripping )
- Man: Is someone there?
- ( Both gasp )
Man: Hey, did you
hear voices just now?
Man 2: It's your imagination.
( Shuffling )
( Door creaking )
Man 1: If it was a stray cat,
I would have
caught it for dinner.
Man 2: You eat
those disgusting things?
( Heavy footsteps )
( Emma gasps )
'ª
( Norman gasps )
( Emma gasps )
( Male demon hisses )
( Laughs )
It looks so delicious.
Human flesh
is definitely the tastiest.
Norman: No.
- ( Liquid sloshing )
- Demon 1: Damn!
I wish I could have
just a fingertip.
Male demon 2: Don't joke.
It's valuable merchandise,
definitely not something
we are meant to enjoy.
The human flesh from this farm
is the highest quality.
Only the rich can afford it.
( Emma whispering ) Where's mom?
Norman: Shh.
Demon 3: How's the gupna?
Demon 2: It's mostly done, sir.
Demon 3: Another six-year-old.
We've only been shipping out
average ones lately,
but we'll be harvesting
some of the high-grade stock
soon enough.
- Right, Isabella?
- Isabella: Yes.
Demon 3: These three
with full marks
are to be prepared for plucking.
Isabella: Yes, sir.
I understand.
Demon 3: Hold on.
I smell something.
'ª
( Both panting )
( Emma gasps )
Norman: You okay?
( Emma gasping )
This place...
Is a farm.
We're all just food?
( Norman panting )
Emma: It can't be.
Didn't everyone go
to foster homes?
And mom is a normal,
loving mother, right?
This is all a mistake!
What we saw wasn't Conny!
How could it be?!
Norman: I'm afraid it was Conny.
( Emma sobbing )
( Wailing )
( Wails echoing )
Ray: Welcome home. How'd it go?
Norman: We didn't
make it in time.
( Stairs creaking )
( Woman humming melody )
Emma: Have we been
living here this whole time
just to end up as food?
Norman: Let's escape, Emma.
We'll get out of here.
That's right. We can do it.
Between you, me, and ray...
Emma: And the others,
what about them?
( Sobs ) I can't leave them.
If we do,
they'll all be killed for sure.
I can't take it.
I don't want to lose
any more family.
( Norman shudders )
( Hummed melody continues )
And you won't have to.
( Emma gasps )
Norman: Try not to worry.
We'll flee, all of us.
Emma: Really? But how?
How can a bunch of kids
run away from those monsters?
( Gasps ) Strategy,
like when we played tag.
Norman: Right.
We will find a way,
one that ensures
all of us survive.
( Emma grunts )
( Hummed melody continues )
( Melody stops )
( Drip echoes )
'ª
( singing in Japanese )